And now we're going to talk about it has an auto focus assist lamp.
And this is an infrared lamp that lights up the area and allows the auto focus to work properly.
And you can basically turn that on or off.
You probably want to keep it on.
And you've also got automatic focus and automatic exposure locks.
So if you set something up like a flower and then you want it to be the same exposure level when a bee flies in, because the bee may change the exposure and the focus, you might want to lock all that down so that it will be done properly as that bee comes across the screen, and you're ready to shoot.
You've also got digital zoom.
Now there’s two kinds of zooms.
There's digital zoom and optical zoom.
Optical is locking in a lot better because you're able to into to something optically and make it larger with the same amount of pixels.
Now the digital zoom, it will basically crop it in the camera and reduce the area of your photograph to a smaller area which will make it look like its zoomed and magnified.